Before you absolutely free builder of one of the most popular styler today, Azorult.

Everything, just like 2x2:

1) Specify the domain on which the styler will knock.
2) Download the archive, which will be build, manual and panel.
3) Install the panel, load the build ...
4) Work 💵💵💵👌🏻.

We have done a great job by changing the admin panel beyond recognition:

🎯 Fixes numerous vulnerabilities and errors of the original panel.

🎯 Acceleration of work from 2 to 8 times.

🎯 Visual statistics by country (the same map of the world).

🎯 Work with reports has become more convenient than ever: convenient commenting of reports has been implemented, pin important reports to the top of the list, color-coded interesting reports.

🎯 View a screenshot and basic information on the report without downloading!

🎯 Changing the status of passwords - now do not have to check the same thing several times!

🎯 So long awaited click & copy for logins and passwords.

🎯 Instead of one tab, the Important Links - you can now specify ANY number of link groups. You can create groups for mail, crypt accounts, forums, freelancing, social networks, etc. how much is enough of your imagination!

🎯 All accounts suitable for a particular group stand out among the rest with the help of a colored plate, it is simply impossible to miss an important account!

🎯 Full functionality of the original steeler - grabbing passwords from browsers, mailers, ftp clients, theft of crypto crates and everything else.

*** And most importantly - UPDATES! 🛠 ***
The panel is updated regularly, errors are corrected and new functions are added!

WE ARE ORIENTED ON A DIALOGUE - YOU CAN BE OFFERING AN IDEA THAT WILL BE IMPLEMENTED IN A NEW VERSION WITH A HIGH PROBABILITY !!!

9/17
Wishes and suggestions, send here:

✉️ gazorp_info@protonmail.com

9/18
Thanks for the feedback, the answers to the recurring questions will be posted on the channel.
September 23 - mini-update.

10/1
Some news:
Check Point conducted a “test drive” and acknowledged that the Gazorp service is working,
as promised, regularly generating instances of Azorult version 3.0.

Specification: we use v3.1.

The above contacts work only on incoming messages. All responses will be posted on the channel, if confidentiality conditions are not violated.
Thank you for being with us.

https://threatpost.ru/dark-web-azorult-generator-offers-free-binaries-to-cybercrooks/28494/
https://threatpost.com/dark-web-azorult-generator-offers-free-binaries-to-cybercrooks/137812/
https://research.checkpoint.com/the-gazorp-dark-web-azorult-builder/